SEBASTIAN DI SALVATORE

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

+(54) 2634761074 | ds.sebastian@outlook.com | MENDOZA, ARGENTINA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front-Desk

Charlotte, NC, USA Jan 2011 - Feb 2012

- Provided technical support for office equipment and resolved technical issues
- Maintained accurate and organized customer records.

Owner, PaintSmart - Remodeling Business

Lawrenceville, GA, USA Feb 2015 - Aug 2018

- Prepared precise cost estimates for construction projects, ensuring adherence to budgets.
- Managed company website, marketing efforts, and maintained client relationships.
- Performed carpentry, painting, kitchen and bathroom remodeling, and other construction tasks.

Freelance Full-Stack Developer

Remote Aug 2023 - Current

• Engaged in freelance projects to pursue a career transition into programming.

EDUCATION

GED

Gwinnet Technical College Lawrenceville, GA, USA Feb 2016 - Jan 2018

Associate in computer science

University of The People

Pasadena, CA, USA Jan 2022 - Aug 2024

• Developed a comprehensive understanding of algorithms, data structures, databases, operating systems, networking, programming, and computer hardware abstraction.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, SASS, TAILWIND, JAVASCRIPT, GIT, REACT, NEXT.JS, TYPESCRIPT, MONGODB, NODE.JS, PHP, EXPRESS.JS, SQL, PYTHON, JAVA, PHOTOSHOP, ILLUSTRATOR.

LINKS

Portfolio GitHub LinkedIn

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full-stack developer with three years of hands-on experience in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Express.js, and a variety of other frameworks. My mission is to blend technical expertise and creative flair to craft captivating user experiences

COURSES & CERTIFICATES

Front-End Engineer,

Codeacademy Dec 2022 - Aug 2023

Full-Stack Developer,

Udemy Dec 2022 - Aug 2023

Advanced CSS and Sass, Udemy Jun 2023 - Oct 2023

LANGUAGES

Spanish

Native

English Bilingual



